[
  {
    "question"         : "あ",
    "answer"           : "a",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "い",
    "answer"           : "i",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "う",
    "answer"           : "u",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "え",
    "answer"           : "e",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "お",
    "answer"           : "o",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "か",
    "answer"           : "ka",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "き",
    "answer"           : "ki",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "く",
    "answer"           : "ku",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "け",
    "answer"           : "ke",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "こ",
    "answer"           : "ko",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "さ",
    "answer"           : "sa",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "し",
    "answer"           : "shi",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "す",
    "answer"           : "su",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "せ",
    "answer"           : "se",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "そ",
    "answer"           : "so",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "た",
    "answer"           : "ta",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ち",
    "answer"           : "chi",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "つ",
    "answer"           : "tsu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "て",
    "answer"           : "te",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "と",
    "answer"           : "to",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "な",
    "answer"           : "na",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "に",
    "answer"           : "ni",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ぬ",
    "answer"           : "nu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ね",
    "answer"           : "ne",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "の",
    "answer"           : "no",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "は",
    "answer"           : "ha",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ひ",
    "answer"           : "hi",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ふ",
    "answer"           : "fu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "へ",
    "answer"           : "he",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ほ",
    "answer"           : "ho",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ま",
    "answer"           : "ma",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "み",
    "answer"           : "mi",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "む",
    "answer"           : "mu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "め",
    "answer"           : "me",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "も",
    "answer"           : "mo",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "や",
    "answer"           : "ya",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ゆ",
    "answer"           : "yu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "よ",
    "answer"           : "yo",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ら",
    "answer"           : "ra",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "り",
    "answer"           : "ri",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "る",
    "answer"           : "ru",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "れ",
    "answer"           : "re",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ろ",
    "answer"           : "ro",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "わ",
    "answer"           : "wa",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "を",
    "answer"           : "wo",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ん",
    "answer"           : "n",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  }
]
